Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- A 3524 - A 3771 (1943). (Box 18)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Ender, Louis, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Gnome Bakers, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Illustrated Soap Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Manhattan Provision Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - R.K. Pastry Baking Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Restaurant Larue, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - San Jacinto Hotel, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Superior Duck Manufacturing Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Reuben, Arnold Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Royal Switchboard Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Brooklyn Standard Bag Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Millinery Firms: Vonie, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Champion Envelope Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Childs Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 91)
- A 3772 - A 3978 (1943). (Box 19)
  - Bliss, E.W. Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Metal Frame Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Assn. Inc., Penn Zone Assn. Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Kinred Hotel Corporation, Operators of Boro Hotel, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Doubleday, Doran Book Shops, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rockford Dairy, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Zamax Mfg. Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bronx Scaffold and Ladder Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Truck Renting Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - C and L Restaurant, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Ledkote Products Co. of N.Y. Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Modern Live Fish Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bergdorf-Goodman, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - American White Cross Laboratories, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Mail Advertising Service Association, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Old Dutch Mustard Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Standard Brands, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Volk, A.A. Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Abacrome, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Arco Metal Craft Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Garment Suppliers Assn Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Kitty Kelly Shoes, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Rosedale Engineering Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Daniel Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Consolidated Service Co. Shelton Solow d/b/a, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Eagle Precision Tool and Die Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Liberty Wrecking, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Magna Products Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Makowsky, J. Corporation, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Rizzo, Joseph, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Harris, M.H. Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Ludwig Baumann Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Triboro Coach Corporation, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - A. Cardani, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Bates Chevrolet Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Nedick's Stores, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Uneeda Credit Stores, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Beyerle Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Clark and Gibby, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Purepac Corporation, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Goodfit Shoe Manufacturing Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Interborough News Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Hygrade Optical, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Aisen Paint Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Progressive Quilting Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Paragon Paint and Varnish Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Wagner Pie Baking Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Morey Machinery Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - B. and H. Aircraft Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Academy Hunter Corporation, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Formfitting Slipper Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - V. La Rosa and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Dutch Masters Paint and Varnish Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - G. Santoro and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - City Provision Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Real Kosher Sausage Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Ajax Bag Shop, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - 41st St. Building Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - National Fisher and Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Eagle Electric Manufacturing Co., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - D.E.H. Demolition Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Dolcort's Pharmacy, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - The Ardun Mechanical Company, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Cigarette Service Inc., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Progressive Doll Accessories Corp., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 69)
- A 3981 - A 4176 (1943). (Box 20)
  - Sperry, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Grennan Bakeries Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Continental Baking Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Quality Mounting and Finishing Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sophia Co. (Franklin Simon Beauty Salon), 1943 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corporation, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Cameo Beauty Depts., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hy-Grade Bag Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - General Baking Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - American Optical Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Murray, A.B. Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Rex Provision Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - City Provision Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Samuelson, A., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Queens Nassau Transit Lines, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - American White Cross Laboratories Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hostess Cake Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Zadek Feldstein Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Zeger, Louis, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Central Coal Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Wheatality Baking Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hanscom Baking Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Warner Furniture, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Z-K Equipment Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fish Forwarding Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Cohn, Sigmund and Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Manufacturers Machine and Tool Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - S. Vogel Hardware, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Guardian Gloss Fur Processing Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Stylecraft Decorators, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Weber, Jules Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Fifth Avenue Tea Room, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Liquidometer Corporation, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Zamay Mfg. Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Optical Research Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Square Deal Market, The, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Pinaud Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - True-Value Slipper and Sandal Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Oxford Handkerchief Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - N.K. Winston Management Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Stuhmer and Co., Geo. F., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Wallace, Burton and Davis, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Dunkel, Samuel and Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Bloch and Guggenheimer, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - A. Krasne, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Sachs Quality Furniture, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Olympia Provision and Baking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Endicott Hotel, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Air Wing Products Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - D.A. Schulte, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Hostess Cake Company, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - X-L Brass Manufacturing Co., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Postman Flour Trucking, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Kay Mfg. Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Ledkote Products Co. of N.Y. inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Modernage Furniture Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Roxy Theatre, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Woolco Realty Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Spencer Arms Hotel, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Lignum Chemical Works, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- A 4181 - A 4549 (1943). (Box 21)
  - U.S. Metal Products, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Victory Tool Laboratories Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Radio Wire Television Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie, Hattie, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Goldsmith Bros., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Parkside Wrecking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Spear and Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Doehler Building Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Steinway Omnibus Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Producers' Laboratories Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Union Square Dental Laboratory, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Liquidometer Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Luxor Hotel and Baths, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Interborough News Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - R.C.A. Communications, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Chauncey Real Estate Co., Ltd., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Millinery Suppliers and Importers Assn., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Jamestown Steel Partitions, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Held Haulage Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Greenwood Cemetery, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Louis Weinberg Associates, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - A. Finkenberg's Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Greater N.Y. Wholesale Liquor Dealers Assn., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Larsen Baking Company, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Read, George R. and Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan News Co., et al., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Feiner, P. and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Reliable Contracting Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Murray, A.B., Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Schuster, Max, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Norwalk Lock Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Supreme Window Cleaning Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of N.Y. Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Consumers Cooperative Service, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Thomas Baking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Krug, George A., Baking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Liberty Wrecking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Metropolitan Window Cleaning Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. of N.Y., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Barton Chocolate Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Grand Wig and Novelty Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Hotel Diplomat, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Flower Box, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Kayser, Julius, Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Childs Company, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Irving Stationery, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Rumal Realty Corp. and Argo Mgmt. Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Interborough News Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - New York Water Service Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Arrowhead Machine and Electric Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Grand Union Furniture Equipment Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Shellcraft Optical Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Childs Company, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Hotel Diplomat, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - PM, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Breakstone Bros., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Greenspan, Simon, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Victoria Vogue, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Blue Ridge Coal Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Sterling Switchboard Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - International Wrecking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - True-Value Slipper and Sandal Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Case Realty Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Milano Bros., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Sun-Ray Baking Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of N.Y., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Consolidated Film Industries, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Sophia Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Phoenix Machine Tool Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Merit Paint, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Werman and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - B.R. Trucking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Purity Bakeries Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Spear Box Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Interborough News Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Q.O.S. Corporation, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Franklin Simon and Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Barry, E.J. Drug Company, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Kay-El Drugs, Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - East Side Chevrolet Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Burndy Engineering Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Tri-Borough Transportation Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corporation, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Gerard Avenue Syndicate, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - California Pie and Baking Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Phoenix Machine Tool Corporation, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - American Vault Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Metropolitan Distributors Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Stolper and Lemisch, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Siegel Trucking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Palace Shoe Rebuilders, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Plaza Shoe Repair, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - East Cost MDSE Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Franklin Simon and Co., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - True-Value Slipper and Sandal Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 101)
- 1/43-1 to 12/43-64 and A 4554 - A 4598 (1943). (Box 22)
  - S. Szczotkowski, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - G. and M. Walkenberg, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Sam Fink, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Myrtle Mfg. Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Aetna Cooperage, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lambrecht Creamery, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Wholesale Hardware and House Furnishings Association, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ronzini Macaroni Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Cortland Valet Service, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fink Baking Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Breyer Ice Cream Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn De Luxe Theatre, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Airwing Products, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Butter and Egg Truckmen, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Phillips Electrical Supply Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Airwing Products, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Ackerly and Sandiford, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Sternberger Motor Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Spring, Crosby, Lafayette Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - WM. Sherman, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Queens Bridge Food Stores, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Gresham Realty Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Durkee Famous Foods, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Joe Lowe Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Uptown Fish Dealers, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Consolidated Cork Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - A. Greenblatt, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Interborough News Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - National Headwear Mfrs. Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Weil Bros., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Mervin Fish Corporations, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Clasp Envelope Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Moore Trucking Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Mayflower Transit Lines, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Bloch and Guggenheimer, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Pitegoff Brothers, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - H. Nussbaum, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Glassoloid Mfg. Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Cooper Stamp Works, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Aero Spark Plug Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Fischer-Berman Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Saw Mill River Realty Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - N.Y. Fruit and Produce Pureyors Assn. Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Capitol Wine and Spirits Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - M. and M. Transportation Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Consolidated Laundries Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Cap Front Manufacturers, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Guardian Gloss Fur Processing Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Ackerman-Gould Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Sal's King Market, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Le Cody Toasted Pies, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Bagel Bakers Association, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Kaufman and Rubin, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Saymont Optical Instrument Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Precision Metal Products Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Metropolitan Funeral Directors Assn., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - S. Horenstein, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Cheesman-Elliot Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Hubert Chemists, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - General Arc Lighting Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Eagle Plastics Corporation, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Atlas Footwear Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Wales Optical Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Kanowitz, M., and Son, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Merit Display Card Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Blue Ribbon Fish Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Mahoney-Clarke, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - H.L. Kosh Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - U.S. Tool Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Warshaw Mfg. Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - 260 Ocean Parkway Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - American Lead Pencil Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Simon and Shapiro, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Hatters Oakhide Boxes Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Gehnrich Corporation, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Assn. Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Jackson Hotel, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Menu Printers Employers Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Keen's English Chop House Corp., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Avon Wrecking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Amity Fur Dressing and Finishing Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Ledkote Products Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Duvernoy Baking Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Kings and Queens Counties Master Barbers Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Novelty Jewelry Manufacturers. Assn., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Pelham Equities, Inc., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 91)
- A 4600 - A 4875 (1944). (Box 23)
  - Regal Kiddie Shop, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Grabstein and Mass, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Gnome Bakers, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Palizzio, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dumont Electric Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cohn, Sigmud and Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Richards Sporting Goods, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Rosedale Engineering Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Spear and Company, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Eagle Precision Tool and Die Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Levy. Bertram, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Duroyd Gasket and Die Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Farrand Optical Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Paramount Pictures, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Kanak Company, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Keller Dorian Paper Company, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Kresge, S.S. Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Fanny Farmer Candy Shops Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Courtade, N.J. and Sons, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Morey Machinery Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Gerard Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Rockwell Baking Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Bates Chevrolet Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Desco Shoe Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Morris, Jack, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Associated Foundries Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Bellacicio Bakery, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Paper Assn. of New York City, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Umbrella Manufacturers. Assn., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Orgler Envelope Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Kollsman Instrument Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Assn., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - American Cystoscope Makers, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Morell's Specialty Shop, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Fairchild Aviation Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - 1980 7th Ave. Co-oper. Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Pinaud, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Title Guaranty and Trust Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Kamen Products Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Saymont Optical Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - French Bakers, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Meyer and Lange, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Conray Products, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Modern Age Furniture Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Rosenfeld and Herring, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Badian Bristle Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Hotel Sharon, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Namm, A.I. Dept. Store, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Nasco Awnings Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Interborough News Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Schoonmaker, A.O. Insulation, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Vogel, Samuel, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - American Ort Federation, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Burndy Engineering Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Green, W. Electric Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Davega City Radio Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Bergdorf and Goodman Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Flat Iron Building, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Coca Cola Bottling Co. of N.Y. Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - 409 Edgecombe Avenue, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Marcus and Miller, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Trenk, Morris, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - United Parcel Service Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Woolco Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Stafford, S.S. Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - N.Y. Assn. of Wholesalers of Ladies' and Children's Hats Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Central Chair Co. Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Victoria Vogue Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Jay Building Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Josephson Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Model Theatre, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Modell, Henry, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Majestic Display Case Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Industrial Electronic Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Macy, R.H. and Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Green Electric Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Rockwell Bakery, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Rockwell Baking Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Fish Fillet Dealers Assn., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Jamaica Buses, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Kuhne, Emil, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - United Scientific Laboratories Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Sani-Aqua Shower Curtains, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Breakstone Bros., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 90)